Guide to the William C. Bullitt Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1882-1967; Series I
  - Foxcroft School, 1937-1942 (Box 30, Folder 666 - 667)
  - France Forever, 1941-1944 (Box 30, Folder 668)
    See also: Series I. Correspondence, 1882-1967 Folder 414
  - Frankfurter, Felix, 1919-1920, 1927, 1933-1934, 1940-1943 (Box 30, Folder 669)
  - Franklin County Public Hospital, 1939-1948, 1957, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 670)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt Library, 1939-1940 (Box 30, Folder 671)
  - Frantz, J. Andrew, 1933, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 672)
  - Frary, William T., 1942-1946 (Box 30, Folder 673)
  - Freedman, Abraham L., 1943-1946, 1953-1961 (Box 30, Folder 674)
  - Fremont, Lucien, 1939-1940 (Box 30, Folder 675)
  - Freud, Alexander, 1942 (Box 30, Folder 676)
  - Freud, Anna, 1939-1940 (Box 30, Folder 677)
  - Freud, Ernest L., 1965-1966 (Box 30, Folder 678)
  - Freud, Esti, 1942-1943 (Box 30, Folder 679)
  - Freud, Harry, 1941-1943 (Box 30, Folder 680)
  - Freud, Sigmund, 1927, 1932-1939, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 681)
    See also: Oversize Folder 38 - 39
  - Friede, Donald, 1933-1934, 1939 (Box 30, Folder 682)
  - Frost, John W., 1959-1966 (Box 30, Folder 683)
  - Fuller, Horace H. and Mrs., 1938-1942 (Box 31, Folder 684)
  - Fuller, Lawrence S., 1940-1942 (Box 31, Folder 685)
  - Fullerton, Hugh S., 1937, 1940-1949, 1955 (Box 31, Folder 686)
  - Furness, Fairman, 1919, 1933-1937, 1943, 1948-1952 (Box 31, Folder 687)
  - Fyfe, Howard, 1940-1942, 1948-1951 (Box 31, Folder 688)
  - G-Git (Box 31, Folder 689 - 711)
  - Gl-Gwy (Box 32, Folder 712 - 734)
  - Gaess, Dorothy, 1940-1943 (Box 32, Folder 735)
  - Galichon, Jean, 1947-1953 (Box 32, Folder 736)
  - Gardner, H. Eugene, 1942-1943, 1948 (Box 32, Folder 737)
  - Garrett, Ethel
    See: Oversize Folder 85
  - Gautier, S. M., 1945-1947 (Box 32, Folder 738)
  - Genay, Renée [includes photographs], 1940-1956 (Box 33, Folder 739)
  - General Motors Export Company
    See: Series I. Correspondence, 1882-1967 Folder 2166
  - George of Greece, Princess, 1938-1941 (Box 33, Folder 740)
  - George, William Perry, 1938-1943 (Box 33, Folder 741)
  - Georgetown University, 1946-1958, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 742 - 745)
  - Gerard, James W., 1937-1949 (Box 33, Folder 746)
  - Germain, Leon C., 1940-1951 (Box 33, Folder 747)
  - Geyelin, H. Rawle, 1933-1940 (Box 33, Folder 748)
  - Gibson, Hugh, 1937-1943, undated (Box 33, Folder 749)
  - Gilbert, Prentiss, 1937-1939 (Box 33, Folder 750)
  - Gilman, Robert, 1938-1951 (Box 33, Folder 751)
  - Gilroy, Dudley and Francesca [includes photographs], 1938-1967 (Box 33, Folder 752 - 753)
  - Girard Trust Company, 1917-1921, 1933-1936, 1940-1944, 1947-1966 (Box 33, Folder 754 - 757)
  - Glass, Irwin, 1941-1951 (Box 33, Folder 758)
  - Glendinning, Virginia, 1947-1948 (Box 33, Folder 759)
  - Glenn, Leslie, 1948-1954 (Box 33, Folder 760)
  - Glover, Wellington, 1945-1949, 1952 (Box 33, Folder 761)
  - Gottlieb, Ephraim, 1938-1940 (Box 33, Folder 762)
  - Gowen, James E., 1942-1944 (Box 33, Folder 763)
  - Grabisch, Agatha, 1919-1937, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 764)
  - Gray, William, 1947-1948 (Box 33, Folder 765)
  - Green, Joseph C., 1935-1939, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 766)
  - Grew, Joseph C., 1916-1919, 1934-1951 (Box 33, Folder 767)
  - Griffin, Isabel and William V., 1910-1917, 1933-1947, 1949-1956, undated (Box 34, Folder 768 - 782)
  - Griswold, Arthur [includes photographs], 1953-1954 (Box 34, Folder 783)
  - Groome, Pierce, 1933-1934 (Box 34, Folder 784)
  - Gross, David, 1940-1942 (Box 34, Folder 785)
  - Guffey, Joseph, 1933-1943 (Box 34, Folder 786)
  - Gunther, John [includes photographs], 1933-1947, undated (Box 34, Folder 787)
  - Guthrie, Hunter, 1946-1957, 1962, undated (Box 34, Folder 788)
  - Gwynn, William, 1936-1943 (Box 34, Folder 789)
  - H-Hap (Box 34, Folder 790 - 797)
  - Har-Hl (Box 35, Folder 798 - 813)
  - Ho-Hy (Box 36, Folder 814 - 827)
  - H. P. Hood and Sons, 1955 (Box 36, Folder 828)
  - Hadassah, 1942 (Box 36, Folder 829)
  - Haddad, Charles, 1940-1942 (Box 36, Folder 830)
  - Hadow, Lindsay and Robert H., 1933, [ca 1944]-1953 (Box 36, Folder 831)
  - Haerdtl-Mor, Alice [includes photograph], 1933-1946 (Box 36, Folder 832)
  - Hahn, Kurt, 1920, 1933-1939 (Box 36, Folder 833)
  - Haight, Gordon S., 1950 (Box 36, Folder 834)
  - Haight, James A., Jr., 1933-1942 (Box 36, Folder 835)
  - Haight, John McVickar, Jr., 1949-1962 (Box 36, Folder 836)
  - Halifax, Edward [includes photograph], 1942-1947 (Box 36, Folder 837)
  - Hallett, Mertie Gillies, 1933 (Box 36, Folder 838)
  - Hampfel, Elizabeth "Sis", 1940-1951 (Box 36, Folder 839)
  - Hansen, N. E., 1933-1934 (Box 36, Folder 840)
  - Hapgood, Elizabeth R., 1934-1947 (Box 36, Folder 841)
  - Harcourt, Brace, and Company, 1925-1927, 1933-1940 (Box 37, Folder 842)
  - Harding, William Knott, 1933-1939 (Box 37, Folder 843)
  - Hare, Elizabeth Sage, 1942-1944 (Box 37, Folder 844)
  - Harper, Donald, 1938-1944 (Box 37, Folder 845)
  - Harper, Samuel N., 1933-1935 (Box 37, Folder 846)
  - Harriman, Florence "Daisy" Jaffrey, 1933-1944 (Box 37, Folder 847)
  - Harriman, William Averell, 1933-1942 (Box 37, Folder 848)
  - Harrison, Nancy, 1938-1944 (Box 37, Folder 849)
  - Hart, Charles D., 1933-1942 (Box 37, Folder 850)
  - Hart, Hornell, 1949 (Box 37, Folder 851)
  - Hartley, Marsden, 1926-1927, 1933-1940, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 852 - 854)
  - Hartman, Edward Albert Edmond, 1941 (Box 37, Folder 855)
  - Hartwell, Edith E. and Harold, 1922, 1933-1959, undated (Box 37, Folder 856 - 857)
  - Hartzell, Arthur E., 1940 (Box 37, Folder 858)
  - Hatch, Richard Warren, 1953-1956 (Box 37, Folder 859)
  - Havens, Vern L., 1933 (Box 37, Folder 860)
  - Haynes, Thornwell, 1919-1920, 1933 (Box 37, Folder 861)
  - Hays, Arthur Garfield, 1929-1930, 1932-1941, 1953 (Box 37, Folder 862)
  - Hayward, Bertrand W., 1950 (Box 37, Folder 863)
  - Hazen, John, 1908-1911, undated (Box 37, Folder 864)
  - Heakin, Harold L., 1940-1943 (Box 37, Folder 865)
  - Heaphy, William, 1941, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 866)
  - Heath, Donald R., 1939, 1950-1954 (Box 37, Folder 867)
  - Heatwole, Oliver, 1954-1955 (Box 37, Folder 868)
  - Hedervary, Khuen, 1947, 1952-1954 (Box 37, Folder 869)
  - Henderson, Alexander "Alec," I, 1942, 1949-1950 (Box 37, Folder 870)
  - Henderson, Loy W., 1934-1960, 1965-1966, undated (Box 38, Folder 871 - 879)
  - Henderson, Roderick R., 1940 (Box 38, Folder 880)
  - Hendrikson, Oskar R., 1947-1949 (Box 38, Folder 881)
  - Henning, Moyra [includes photographs], 1936-1938, 1946-1948, undated (Box 38, Folder 882)
  - Henry-Haye, D., 1939-1940 (Box 38, Folder 883)
  - Henry-Haye, Gaston, 1939-1943, 1950, 1955 (Box 38, Folder 884)
  - Herter, Christian, 1918, 1922, 1943-1947, 1955 (Box 38, Folder 885)
  - Heurteux, Maurice, 1941-1943, 1956 (Box 38, Folder 886)
  - Hibbon, Paxton, 1922 (Box 38, Folder 887)
  - Higgins, Elizabeth, 1937-1943, 1951 (Box 38, Folder 888)
  - Higgins, Lawrence, 1936-1941, [ca 1954] (Box 38, Folder 889)
  - Higgins, Marion "Dearie", 1938-1942, 1952 (Box 38, Folder 890)
  - Hillenkoetter, Jane and Jay, 1952-1957 (Box 38, Folder 891)
  - Hillenkoetter, Roscoe H., 1933-1947, 1950-1956, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 892 - 893)
  - Hillman, Alex, 1950 (Box 38, Folder 894)
  - Hills, Lawrence, 1936-1942 (Box 38, Folder 895)
  - Himran, Naciye, 1943-1947, 1956-1957 (Box 38, Folder 896)
  - Hodges, Charles, 1933-1938 (Box 38, Folder 897)
  - Hoff, Trygve J. B., 1946-1947 (Box 38, Folder 898)
  - Hoffman, Ernest A., 1941 (Box 38, Folder 899)
  - Hoffman, Sal B., 1951 (Box 38, Folder 900)
  - Hoke, Millard J., 1942 (Box 39, Folder 901)
  - Holliday, Michael "Mickey", 1940-1943 (Box 39, Folder 902)
  - Holt, Eugene J., 1941-1943 (Box 39, Folder 903)
  - Hooker, Harry S., 1937-1941 (Box 39, Folder 904)
  - Hooper, Alice Forbes Perkins, 1936-1944 (Box 39, Folder 905 - 907)
  - Hoover, Herbert, 1938-1954, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 908)
  - Hoover, J. Edgar, 1941-1947, 1957 (Box 39, Folder 909)
  - Hopkins, Charles, 1938-1941 (Box 39, Folder 910)
  - Hopkins, Ernest Martin, 1939-1943 (Box 39, Folder 911)
  - Hopkins, Harry L., 1937-1941 (Box 39, Folder 912)
  - Hopper, Bruce C., 1933-1951 (Box 39, Folder 913 - 914)
  - Horn, Max, 1938-1942 (Box 39, Folder 915)
  - Hornbeck, Stanley K., 1934-1954, 1962, 1965-1966 (Box 39, Folder 916)
  - Horter, Elizabeth, 1933-1943 (Box 39, Folder 917)
  - Horton, John Wells, 1940 (Box 39, Folder 918)
  - Horwitz, George, Jon, and Marian, 1953-1959 (Box 39, Folder 919)
  - Horwitz, Nataline Dulles, [ca 1934], [ca 1941]-1955, undated (Box 39, Folder 920)
  - Horwitz, Orville, 1933-1960, 1965, undated (Box 39, Folder 921 - 922)
  - Hoskins, Harold B., 1941 (Box 39, Folder 923)
  - Hotchkiss, Julia S., 1940-1941 (Box 39, Folder 924)
  - Houghton, William M., 1933-1939 (Box 39, Folder 925)
  - Houghton, Woodson, 1954-1967 (Box 39, Folder 926)
  - House, Edward M., 1917-1919, 1930-1936 (Box 40, Folder 927 - 929)
  - House, Irwin L., [ca 1942] (Box 40, Folder 930)
  - Howard, Roy W., 1936-1954 (Box 40, Folder 931)
  - Howe, Arthur, 1933-1934 (Box 40, Folder 932)
  - Howe, Arthur W., Jr., 1939-1942 (Box 40, Folder 933)
  - Howe, Frederick C., 1933-1938 (Box 40, Folder 934)
  - Howe, George, 1934-1959 (Box 40, Folder 935)
  - Howell, Humphrey D., 1933-1934 (Box 40, Folder 936)
  - Howell, Letty, 1940-1944 (Box 40, Folder 937)
  - Hrones, John, 1934, 1940-1942, 1958 (Box 40, Folder 938)
  - Huber-Besch, Gusti, 1947 (Box 40, Folder 939)
  - Huddleston, Sisley, 1936, 1948-1952, undated (Box 40, Folder 940)
  - Hudson, Manley O., 1933, 1936, 1944, undated (Box 40, Folder 941)
  - Huffer, Herman Charles, Jr., 1938-1942 (Box 40, Folder 942)
  - Hughes, Charles Evans, 1938-1941 (Box 40, Folder 943)
  - Hull, Cordell, 1933-1946, 1948 (Box 40, Folder 944 - 946)
  - Hull, George R., 1939-1942 (Box 40, Folder 947)
  - Hulley, Benjamin M., 1940-1941 (Box 40, Folder 948)
  - Hunneman, William C., 1933, 1941-1944 (Box 40, Folder 949)
  - Hunter, Edward, 1939-1942 (Box 40, Folder 950)
  - Hurteau, Lucien H., 1934-1944, undated (Box 40, Folder 951)
  - Hutchins, Kenneth, 1940-1941 (Box 40, Folder 952)
  - Hyde, James, 1935, 1937-1947 (Box 40, Folder 953)
  - Ia-In (Box 40, Folder 954 - 955)
  - Is-Iw (Box 41, Folder 956 - 958)
  - I Fu-de, 1952-1955 (Box 41, Folder 959)
  - Ickes, Harold L., 1933-1948 (Box 41, Folder 960)
  - Ickes, Jane D., 1938-1953 (Box 41, Folder 961)
  - Immanuel, Max, 1937-1943 (Box 41, Folder 962)
  - Ingersoll, C. Jared, 1941-1946 (Box 41, Folder 963)
  - Ingersoll, R. Sturgis, 1933-1955, undated (Box 41, Folder 964 - 968)
  - Ingersoll, Rita S., 1932-1940 (Box 41, Folder 969)
  - Ingling, Dorothy R., 1948-1950 (Box 41, Folder 970)
  - International News Service, 1947 (Box 41, Folder 971)
  - Isaacson, Pauline, 1955-1956 (Box 41, Folder 972)
  - Ismail, Refik [includes photographs], 1928-1949 (Box 41, Folder 973)
  - J-Jn (Box 41, Folder 974 - 980)
  - Jo-Jw (Box 42, Folder 981 - 989)
  - J. and L. Lobmeyr, 1936-1939, 1952 (Box 42, Folder 990)
  - Jackson, C. D., 1939-1941, undated (Box 42, Folder 991)
  - Jacobs, Sophia, 1942-1943 (Box 42, Folder 992)
  - Jessup, Philip, 1949 (Box 42, Folder 993)
  - Jester, Perry N., 1942 (Box 42, Folder 994)
  - Johnson, Albin E., 1933 (Box 42, Folder 995)
  - Johnson, Alvin, 1933-1941 (Box 42, Folder 996)
  - Johnson, Hiram W., 1934-1943 (Box 42, Folder 997)
  - Johnson, Owen, 1933-1936 (Box 42, Folder 998)
  - Jones, Eleanor Benton "Happy", 1940-1947 (Box 42, Folder 999 - 1000)
  - Jones, Ernest, 1955-1956 (Box 42, Folder 1001)
  - Jones, Jesse H., 1939-1953 (Box 42, Folder 1002 - 1004)
  - Judd, Walter H., 1947-1951 (Box 42, Folder 1005)
  - Judson, Arthur, 1941-1951 (Box 42, Folder 1006)
  - Judson, George A., 1937-1938 (Box 42, Folder 1007)
  - K (Box 43, Folder 1008 - 1038)
  - Kaltenborn, H. V., 1933-1943 (Box 44, Folder 1039)
  - Kane, Edward J., 1940-1941 (Box 44, Folder 1040)
  - Karszo-Siedlewski, Jan, 1947-1949 (Box 44, Folder 1041)
  - Kastner, Max [includes photographs], 1933-1967, undated (Box 44, Folder 1042 - 1044)
  - Kaynor, W. F. [includes photographs], 1935-1942 (Box 44, Folder 1045 - 1048)
  - Keedick, Lee, 1940-1941, 1949 (Box 44, Folder 1049)
  - Keiser, Lawrence B. and Marion [includes photographs], 1948-1957, undated (Box 44, Folder 1050 - 1052)
  - Keith, Eliza Horne, 1933-1941, 1961-1964 (Box 44, Folder 1053)
  - Keith, William Scott, 1934, 1941-1950 (Box 44, Folder 1054)
  - Keller, Albert G., 1948-1950, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 1055)
  - Keller, James, 1950 (Box 44, Folder 1056)
  - Kelley, Jack, 1940-1941 (Box 44, Folder 1057)
  - Kelley, Robert F., 1934-1948, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 1058)
  - Kempner, Robert N. W., 1940-1941, 1948 (Box 44, Folder 1059)
  - Kennan, George Frost, 1933-1947, 1955 (Box 44, Folder 1060 - 1062)
  - Kennedy, John F., 1939-1960, undated (Box 44, Folder 1063)
  - Kennedy, Joseph P. and Rose [and aides], 1936-1943, undated (Box 45, Folder 1064 - 1069)
  - Kennedy, Sinclair, 1941
    See: Oversize Folder 89
  - Kent, Frank R., 1945-1953 (Box 45, Folder 1070)
  - Kerherve, Jean, 1942-1943, 1957-1965 (Box 45, Folder 1071)
  - Keyser-Got, Ethel
  - Kimball, Fiske, 1934, 1941, 1950 (Box 45, Folder 1072)
  - Kindler, Hans, 1933-1949 (Box 45, Folder 1073)
  - King, Herbert Thomas [includes photograph], 1954-1956 (Box 45, Folder 1074)
  - Kingsford, Frances, 1939-1943 (Box 45, Folder 1075)
  - Kirk, Alexander C., 1938-1946 (Box 45, Folder 1076)
  - Kirstein, Lincoln, 1933-1934 (Box 45, Folder 1077)
  - Knecht, Marcel, 1937-1940, undated (Box 45, Folder 1078)
  - Knickerbocker, H. R., 1933-1947 (Box 45, Folder 1079)
  - Knopf, Alfred A., 1934-1950 (Box 45, Folder 1080 - 1081)
  - Knowland, W. F., 1949-1955 (Box 45, Folder 1082)
  - Knox, Frank, 1941-1944 (Box 45, Folder 1083)
  - Koenigsberg, M., 1933-1944, undated (Box 45, Folder 1084 - 1086)
  - Kohlberg, Alfred, 1946-1956 (Box 46, Folder 1087 - 1091)
  - Koo, V. K. Wellington, 1938-1940, 1947-1954 (Box 46, Folder 1092 - 1093)
  - Korea, Republic of, Embassy, 1953-1956 (Box 46, Folder 1094)
  - Kotcka, Joseph [includes photographs], 1941-1948 (Box 46, Folder 1095 - 1097)
  - Krestinski, N. N., 1935 (Box 46, Folder 1098)
  - Kris, W. Ernst, 1940 (Box 46, Folder 1099)
  - Kühn, Svend Erik, 1914-1920 (Box 46, Folder 1100)
  - Kuhn, Hedwig S., 1940 (Box 46, Folder 1101)
  - Kung, H. H., 1947-1956 (Box 46, Folder 1102)
  - Kuniholm, Bertel, 1935-1952 (Box 46, Folder 1103)
  - Kuo, Peter, 1952-1962 (Box 46, Folder 1104)
  - L-Laz (Box 46, Folder 1105 - 1118)
  - Le-Ll (Box 47, Folder 1119 - 1141)
  - Lo-Ly (Box 48, Folder 1142 - 1152)
  - LaChambre, Guy and Jeanne, 1938-1964 (Box 48, Folder 1153 - 1155)
  - Lacy, William S. B., 1950-1955, undated (Box 48, Folder 1156)
  - LaFollette, Philip F., 1933-1956 (Box 48, Folder 1157)
  - LaFollette, Robert M., Jr., 1935-1946 (Box 48, Folder 1158)
  - LaGuardia, Fiorello H., 1941-1942 (Box 48, Folder 1159)
  - Laidler, Harry W., 1922-1944 (Box 48, Folder 1160)
  - Lamont, Thomas W., 1918, 1935-1947 (Box 48, Folder 1161)
  - Lamport, S. C., 1933-1934 (Box 48, Folder 1162)
  - Lancaster, William W., 1933-1934 (Box 48, Folder 1163)
  - Lane, Arthur Bliss and Cornelia Baldwin, 1937-1953 (Box 48, Folder 1164)
  - Lange, Fred G., 1940-1950 (Box 48, Folder 1165)
  - Langer, William L., 1945-1950 (Box 48, Folder 1166)
    See also: Series III. Writings, 1888-1984 Folder 715 - 723
  - Langeron, Roger, 1946, 1961-1962 (Box 48, Folder 1167)
  - Langner, Lawrence, 1933-1942 (Box 48, Folder 1168 - 1169)
  - Lansbury, George, 1919-1938 (Box 48, Folder 1170)
  - Laughlin, Henry A., 1940-1962 (Box 49, Folder 1171 - 1172)
  - Laugier, Henri, 1940-1962, undated (Box 49, Folder 1173 - 1174)
  - Lauter, Beatrice, 1954-1965 (Box 49, Folder 1175)
  - Lawrence, David L., 1938-1943 (Box 49, Folder 1176)
  - Leach, Agnes and Henry Goodard, 1934-1941 (Box 49, Folder 1177)
  - Leahy, William D., 1941-1957 (Box 49, Folder 1178)
  - Leary, Mary Elizabeth, 1938-1953 (Box 49, Folder 1179 - 1180)
  - LeHand, Marguerite "Missy", 1933-1944, undated (Box 49, Folder 1181 - 1193)
  - Leigh, W. Colston, 1940-1952 (Box 50, Folder 1194)
  - Leroy, Amé, 1940-1941 (Box 50, Folder 1195)
  - Levine, Isaac Don, 1933-1956 (Box 50, Folder 1196)
  - Levitas, S. M., 1941-1953 (Box 50, Folder 1197 - 1198)
  - Levy, Isaac D., 1940-1943 (Box 50, Folder 1199)
  - Lewis, James Hamilton and Rose Douglas, 1935, 1937-[ca 1940] (Box 50, Folder 1200)
  - Lewis, Sinclair, 1933, 1939 (Box 50, Folder 1201)
  - Life Magazine, 1938-1952, 1965 (Box 50, Folder 1202 - 1203)
  - Lindeberg, Ann, 1949, undated (Box 50, Folder 1204)
  - Lindeberg, Harrie T., 1933-1951, 1956-1959, undated (Box 50, Folder 1205 - 1206)
  - Lindsley, Lorna, 1938-1943, undated (Box 50, Folder 1207)
  - Lippitt, Henry, 1950-1951 (Box 50, Folder 1208)
  - Lippitt, Marion Almy [includes photograph], 1911-1916, 1933-1948, 1966-1967, undated (Box 50, Folder 1209 - 1211)
  - Lippmann, Walter, 1919, 1940-1947, undated (Box 50, Folder 1212)
  - Lisle, Clifton, 1940-1946 (Box 50, Folder 1213)
  - Litvinov, Maxim [includes photographs], 1933-1936, undated (Box 50, Folder 1214)
  - Liu, Tony L. J., 1954-1962 (Box 50, Folder 1215)
  - Lob, Dorothy "Dota" and Erich, 1942-1943 (Box 50, Folder 1216)
  - Lodge, Henry Cabot, Jr., 1946-1967 (Box 50, Folder 1217 - 1218)
  - Loeb, William, Jr., 1933-1956 (Box 50, Folder 1219)
  - Long, Breckinridge, 1934-1942, undated (Box 50, Folder 1220)
  - Long, Elizabeth, 1933-1941, undated (Box 50, Folder 1221)
  - Look Magazine
    General
    See: Series I. Correspondence, 1882-1967 Folder 462
  - Lorenz, Gabriel, 1940-1944 (Box 51, Folder 1222 - 1223)
  - Lotfallah, Habib, 1936-1948 (Box 51, Folder 1224)
  - Lothian, Lord [Kerr, Philip], 1933-1940 (Box 51, Folder 1225)
  - Lovestone, Jay, 1949-1962 (Box 51, Folder 1226)
  - Lovett, Robert A., 1938-1948 (Box 51, Folder 1227)
  - Luce, Clare Booth, 1941-1950 (Box 51, Folder 1228)
  - Luce, Henry R., 1938-1964, undated (Box 51, Folder 1229 - 1231)
  - Lukasiewicz, Julius, Jr., 1948-1949, 1962 (Box 51, Folder 1232)
  - Lukasiewicz, Julius, Sr., 1936-1951 (Box 51, Folder 1233)
  - Lynch, Robert E., 1920-1942, undated (Box 51, Folder 1234)
  - Lyons, Eugene, 1933-1950 (Box 51, Folder 1235 - 1236)
  - Lyttleton, Oliver, 1942-1954 (Box 51, Folder 1237)
  - Ma-Man (Box 51, Folder 1238 - 1243)
  - Mar-Mcv (Box 52, Folder 1244 - 1263)
  - Mea-Mor (Box 53, Folder 1264 - 1297)
  - Mos-Myl (Box 54, Folder 1298 - 1309)
  - M. Knoedler and Company, 1946, 1956 (Box 54, Folder 1310)
  - MacArthur, Douglas, 1934, 1952-1953 (Box 54, Folder 1311)
  - MacArthur, Douglas, II, 1934-1953 (Box 54, Folder 1312 - 1315)
  - MacGowan, Kenneth, 1930-1941 (Box 54, Folder 1316)
  - Machugh, Joseph V., 1940-1953 (Box 54, Folder 1317)
  - MacJannet, Donald R., 1933-1941 (Box 54, Folder 1318)
  - Mack, Harriet T., 1934-1939 (Box 54, Folder 1319)
  - Mack, Julian W., 1933-1935 (Box 54, Folder 1320)
  - MacKay, Henry S., Jr., 1933 (Box 54, Folder 1321)
  - MacLeish, Ada and Archibald, 1933-1951 (Box 54, Folder 1322 - 1323)
  - Macmillan and Company, 1947-1948 (Box 54, Folder 1324)
  - MacMurray, John Van A. [includes photographs], 1933-1939 (Box 54, Folder 1325)
  - MacVeagh, John H., 1938 (Box 54, Folder 1326)
  - Magruder, James, 1956 (Box 54, Folder 1327)
  - Maier, Ruth B., 1942 (Box 54, Folder 1328)
  - Mallory, Margaret, 1947 (Box 54, Folder 1329)
  - Mallory, Walter H., 1933-1942 (Box 54, Folder 1330)
  - Malmed, A. T., 1933 (Box 54, Folder 1331)
  - Malone, Dudley Field, 1933-1934 (Box 54, Folder 1332)
  - Malone, George W., 1947-1948 (Box 55, Folder 1333 - 1334)
  - Mandel, Benjamin, 1940-1952 (Box 55, Folder 1335)
  - Mandel, H., 1940-1941 (Box 55, Folder 1336)
  - Mann, Garner B., 1944 (Box 55, Folder 1337)
  - Mann, Thomas, 1940 (Box 55, Folder 1338)
  - Manning, John E., 1952-1953 (Box 55, Folder 1339)
  - Marcus, James Anthony, 1934-1956 (Box 55, Folder 1340)
  - Marcus, Joseph A., 1933-1942 (Box 55, Folder 1341)
  - Margolin, Arnold D., 1938-1940 (Box 55, Folder 1342)
  - Mark Twain Society, 1937-1939 (Box 55, Folder 1343)
  - Marriner, J. Theodore, 1933-1937 (Box 55, Folder 1344)
  - Marshall, George W., 1947-1948 (Box 55, Folder 1345)
  - Marshall, H. T., 1942-1956 (Box 55, Folder 1346)
  - Martelo, Vincente Martinez, 1947-1948 (Box 55, Folder 1347)
  - Martin, Jackie, 1933-1942 (Box 55, Folder 1348)
  - Martine, Albert, 1962-1966, undated (Box 55, Folder 1349)
  - Maryknoll Sisters, 1953-1958 (Box 55, Folder 1350)
  - Masie, Hans, 1939 (Box 55, Folder 1351)
  - Mason, Frank E., 1926-1946 (Box 55, Folder 1352)
  - Mathews, Frederic, 1933-1935 (Box 55, Folder 1353)
  - Mathews, William R., 1935-1955 (Box 55, Folder 1354)
  - Mathie, Anna, 1943-1947 (Box 55, Folder 1355)
  - Matthews, H. Freeman, 1937-1943 (Box 55, Folder 1356)
  - Matthews, William R., 1940-1946 (Box 55, Folder 1357)
  - Maurois, Simone André, 1939-1943 (Box 55, Folder 1358)
  - Maverick, Maury, 1935-1940 (Box 55, Folder 1359)
  - Mavrikes, Nicholas [includes photographs], 1938 (Box 55, Folder 1360)
  - Mayer, Charles T., 1948-1953 (Box 55, Folder 1361 - 1363)
  - Maynard, John A. F., 1935-1941 (Box 56, Folder 1364)
  - Mayo, George E., 1946-1948 (Box 56, Folder 1365)
  - Mazot, Henri, 1935-1938 (Box 56, Folder 1366)
  - McCallum, George B., 1933-1938 (Box 56, Folder 1367)
  - McCarran, Pat, 1949-1954 (Box 56, Folder 1368)
  - McCarthy, Joseph R., 1952-1953 (Box 56, Folder 1369)
  - McCloskey, Matthew H., 1936-1937 (Box 56, Folder 1370)
  - McCloy, John J., 1942-1948 (Box 56, Folder 1371)
  - McCoy, Frank, 1940-1943 (Box 56, Folder 1372)
  - McDaniel, Charles B., 1926-1945 (Box 56, Folder 1373)
  - McDonald, Stewart, 1938-1943 (Box 56, Folder 1374)
  - McHugh, James M., 1935-1947, undated (Box 56, Folder 1375)
    See also: Oversize Folder 89
  - McIntire, Charles C., 1931-1940 (Box 56, Folder 1376)
  - McIntyre, Marvin H., 1933-1943 (Box 56, Folder 1377)
  - McKenzie, Mary Willis, 1939 (Box 56, Folder 1378)
  - McLaughlin, Harrison L., 1947-1954 (Box 56, Folder 1379)
  - McLean, Evalyn W., 1934-1942 (Box 56, Folder 1380)
  - McMullan, James, 1921-1947 (Box 56, Folder 1381)
  - Meek, Samuel W., 1940-1955 (Box 56, Folder 1382)
  - Mellon, Leslie, 1955-1961 (Box 56, Folder 1383)
  - Mendl, Charles, 1940-1941 (Box 56, Folder 1384)
  - Mendl, Elsie, 1936-1942 (Box 56, Folder 1385)
  - Mercier, Pierre, 1943, undated (Box 56, Folder 1386)
  - Merck, George, 1933-1954 (Box 56, Folder 1387)
  - Merkel, John, 1950 (Box 56, Folder 1388)
  - Merrel, Clay, 1938-1942 (Box 56, Folder 1389)
  - Merrill, Keith, 1933-1935 (Box 56, Folder 1390)
  - Merzbach, Alice, 1941-1947 (Box 56, Folder 1391)
  - Messersmith, George S., 1934-1947 (Box 56, Folder 1392 - 1395)
  - Metzenbaum, James, 1934 (Box 56, Folder 1396)
  - Meyer, Annie Nathan, 1933-1947 (Box 56, Folder 1397)
  - Meyer, Erna [includes photographs], 1937-1953 (Box 57, Folder 1398 - 1400)
  - Meyer, Fritz, 1933-1953 (Box 57, Folder 1401 - 1405)
  - Milholland, Jean, 1919, 1933-1934 (Box 57, Folder 1406)
  - Miller, Irvin J., 1940-1941 (Box 57, Folder 1407)
  - Mills, Caris E., 1933-1953 (Box 57, Folder 1408)
  - Minor, George C., 1938 (Box 57, Folder 1409)
  - Moën, Lars, 1934-1941 (Box 57, Folder 1410)
  - Moffat, Pierrepont, 1936-1943 (Box 57, Folder 1411)
  - Moley, Raymond, 1933-1935 (Box 57, Folder 1412)
  - Monnet, J. G., 1936-1939 (Box 57, Folder 1413)
  - Monnet, Jean, 1933-1934, 1936- 1954 (Box 57, Folder 1414 - 1415)
  - Montgomery, Minou, 1941-1942 (Box 57, Folder 1416)
  - Montobbio, Ygnacio, 1936-1937 (Box 57, Folder 1417)
  - Moore, R. Walton, 1933-1941 (Box 58, Folder 1418 - 1442)
  - Mora, Armand, 1947-1952 (Box 59, Folder 1443)
  - Morales, German, 1934-1939 (Box 59, Folder 1444)
  - Moranz, Vincent J., 1943 (Box 59, Folder 1445)
  - Morgan and Cie., 1929-1962, undated (Box 59, Folder 1446 - 1447)
  - Morgenthau, Henry, 1933-1947 (Box 59, Folder 1448 - 1449)